

#### **PROFILE**

Hello, I am Ceyhun, I am 31 years old, I am a computer engineer. I am improving myself in software, I am open to further development. I continue to provide remote services as a software engineer for NextGen Software in the USA(remote). My latest professional projects and the languages I actively use are included in my CV.

#### COMMUNICATION

Nationality: T.C

Telephone Number: +90 545 616 1043

E-Mail:

ceyhun.canyurt@gmail.com

Address: Gediz/Kütahya

Marital status :

Date of birth: 18.05.1992

Linkedin:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/ceyhuncanyurt-652ba8225/

#### **HOBBY**

Football Volleyball Ping pong Basketball

# CEYHUN CANYURT

### Software Engineer

#### **EDUCATION**

Dumlupinar University Department of Computer Engineering

Simav Anatolian Teacher High School

#### **SOFTWARE SKILLS**

React, Angular, Unity, Javascript, Typescript, Html, CSS, Python,

AWS(Amazon Web Services), Dynomo Db, PI/Pg SQL, My/Ms SQL,

Postman, Flask, Vue.js, Nuxt.js, Next.js, Tailwind

#### PROFESSIONAL PROJECT

**Professional Web Site** Professional sites that I built the following web applications, you can see as referance:

**nextgensoftware.us** (vue.js, nuxt.js), **trendygets.com** (nuxt.js, tailwind)

**Iris Recognition System** Matlab Dissertation is a desktop application with Oracle Db. I used the Casia iris dataset as an example. You can add new irises to the database and check for matches with previously added irises

**Extension Project** I am involved in the development of a Google Extension Project that covers both web and mobile applications. In this project, I implemented an API using Python and Flask for seamless communication between the extension and the web interface. The architecture includes a combination of React and Angular and provides a robust and dynamic user experience.

To enhance data retrieval, I incorporated a Scraper component utilizing Selenium. This powerful tool extracts data from web pages and efficiently stores it in AWS DynamoDB, ensuring a streamlined and organized database.

You can visit the site and application I prepared for paypeek.com.

**Paypal Payment System** I added the paypal payment system to the **tier25.com** site using the paypal APIs.

#### **JOB EXPERIENCE**

## SOFTWARE ENGINEER – NextGen Software– 01/01/2022 – NOW – BOCA, USA (remote)

(Web-Mobile – I code the website and extenion application. Angular and React applied projects are over, now I have received feedback for the C# project and started developing it. I actively use many software languages and technologies that I have incorporated. I have written websites according to customer demand and there are ongoing projects..)

## UNITY DEVELOPER – Unlimited Education Services - 01/09/2021 – 15/12/2021 – ISTANBUL, TURKIYE

(I took part in the English game and application project for the smart board system of the schools in the software team affiliated with the publishing house company. I experienced my Unity and c # knowledge from here.)

## SOFTWARE DEVELOPER – Medikal Sofware - 01/07/2021 – 01/09/2021 – ISTANBUL, TURKIYE

(I took part in the team that provides technical support for MR and Tomography devices in hospitals. I gained experience by using SQI varieties in this institution.)